# KOREY B. LUU

Mission Viejo, California | (949) 499-4239 | koreyluu@gmail.com

# **SUMMARY**

I am currently learning object oriented programming and C++ with plans to transfer to a 4- year university. I am a motivated and passionate individual currently seeking to broaden his scope in IT and customer service. With many years in the customer service industry, I have gained many leadership and team management skills. These skills have allowed me to understand how to assist with clients' needs and be a good leader. I hope to use these skills to further company progress in the future.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Saddleback Community College

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

#### Skills

- ❖ Java: Object-Oriented Programming
- **♦** C++

- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Office

❖ Adobe Photoshop

**Expected Graduation Date: June 2022** 

❖ Adobe Premiere Pro

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Ding Tea Mission Viejo

Shift Lead

September 2018 - June 2020

Mission Viejo, CA

- Served as a liaison between management & non-management team members by communicating tasks to team members.
- Reported disciplinary issues and customer service complaints to management and dealt with any concerns customers had.
- Maintained inventories by replenishing tea leaves supply, preparing tapioca pearls, resupplying cups, straws, etc.
- Assisted in creating a shift schedule and monitored team performance to ensure that duties are performed efficiently.
- Enhanced the shop's reputation by greeting customers, educating customers on tea drinks, and preparing drinks properly.
- Opened and closed registers by accounting for the daily intake and recording the revenues and expenses per day.

# Surfin Donuts

Manager/Server

December 2014 – March 2019 Mission Viejo, CA

- Established optimal guest experience by seating guests, taking orders, serving dishes, and removing dishwares from tables.
- Managed orders and accompanying financial transactions using the digital Point of Sale system within the organization.
- \* Assisted colleagues and management team during rush hours and promoted teamwork while providing exceptional service.
- Identified and analyzed business issues and proposed solutions to management to enhance the increase of net profit.
- Responsible for the hiring and on-boarding process that included but not limited to interviewing and training of staff.
- Guaranteed accurate records and sufficient supplies by conducting weekly inventories of food, beverages, and materials.

## **VOLUNTEER COMMITMENTS**

#### Boys & Girls Club

Coach/Front Desk Receptionist

March 2020 - December 2020

- San Juan, CA
- Coached an inter-league children's basketball team of 6+ on the rules, teamwork, and techniques needed for basketball.
- Evaluated and identified the players strengths and weaknesses to position them in a team and optimize performance.
- Supervised the children during their break time off from basketball and ensured safety and discipline when needed.
- Greeted and welcomed the children and parents by providing a great first impression and answering any questions.
- Collaborated with other coaches and staff with the sports equipment and planned meetings to create activities for students.